挺晚了  你觉得我们
It's pretty late. You think we got time
有时间再模拟运行一下冷却系统吗
to run somemore simulations on the cooling system?
可以啊  我也还在想怎么弄热声扩展器
Sure, I'm still figuring out the thermoacoustic expander.
你们弄吧  我打算
Oh, while you do that I am going to
去让脑脊髓液重新流过我的大脑细胞
pump cerebral spinal fluid through my brain cells
好消除今日思考所产生的代谢副产品
to remove the metabolic by-products of the day's thoughts.
什么鬼
What?
俗称"睡觉"  我睡觉时间到了
It's called sleep and it's my bedtime.
晚安了  两位
Nighty-night, y'all.
喂喂喂  你别想跑
Hey, hey, hey, you're not going anywhere.
我们只有短短两个月就得交货给空军
We only have two months to deliver this to the Air Force
全是拜你所赐
because of you.
我知道啊  当时我在场呢
I know, I was there.
快给我醒来
Well, wake up!
我们经常得加班到深夜呢
We're gonna put in a lot of late nights.
加到多晚
How late?
谁知道啊  到半夜12点或1点吧
Well, I don't know, midnight, 1:00.
到1点啊
One o'clock?
我又不是小浣熊
I'm not a raccoon.
你要是累了  就去喝点咖啡
If you're tired, have some coffee.
什么  你才该去喝咖啡吧
What? You have some coffee.
我正喝着呢
I am having coffee!
-你看你喝完人多暴躁  -两位
- And look how irritable it's making you! - Guys!
只要一开始吵架  肯定啥也干不了了
We're not gonna get anything done if we start fighting.
你能不能爷们点  撑过去
Now, can you please try to soldier through?
好吧
Fine.
我觉得我撑不了多久了
I don't think I can go much longer.
才过了三分半钟好吗  给我醒来
It's been three and a half minutes, wake up!
我做了一个恶梦  梦到我最好的朋友
I had a bad dream that my best friend became a tyrant
变成了一个暴君  逼我彻夜工作
and forced me to stay up all night to work.
我做了一个美梦  梦到我抱你上床睡时
Oh, I had a good dream that when I carried you to bed,
你的头撞到墙  然后我开怀大笑
I let your head hit the wall and I laughed.
早安
Good morning.
这是在干嘛
What is this?
我们昨晚都没见着你们
Well, we didn't see you last night,
今天也见不到你们
we're not gonna see you today,
所以就想好歹一起吃顿早饭
so we thought we could have breakfast together.
这样真好
Oh, that is so nice.
真的会疼呢
Ow, it does hurt!
所以你们今天打算干嘛
So, what are you guys gonna do today?
本来今天下午谢尔顿该陪我去个派对
Well, Sheldon was supposed to go to this party with me this afternoon,
但我想这事是没戏了
but I don't think that's happening.
从一开始就没有戏过
Oh, that was never happening.
那我陪你去
Oh, I'll go.
我喜欢参加派对
I like a party.
不瞒你说  不是平常说的那种"派对"
Well, to be honest, it's not like a "party" party,
反而更像是个聚会
it's more like a gathering
就是不同领域的科学家们聚集在一起
where scientists of different disciplines get together
分享研究成果
to share their work
以及讨论其他科研领域的最新情况
and keep current on what's going on in other fields.
我也不知道我为啥称这为派对  对不起
I don't know why I called it a party, sorry.
没关系  我还是愿意去
It's okay, I'll still go.
你不觉得你会感到无聊吗
You don't think you'll be bored?
我就喝点酒
Oh, I'll have some wine
然后听听别人聊点我屁都不懂的事情
and listen to people go on about crap I don't understand.
这跟我每天的生活又有什么不同呢
I mean, how is it any different than every single day of my life?
可我不会在场啊
I won't be there.
哎妈  还真是个派对
Look at that, it is a party.
抱歉我整个周末都得工作
Sorry I have to work all weekend.
没关系
It's okay.
谢谢你为我做早餐
Thanks again for breakfast.
昨晚都没等到你回家
Well, I didn't get to see you last night.
臣妾只想尽一点绵力
It was the least I could do.
皇上你就不应该把家门密码设那贱人生日
You shouldn't have made the alarm code his birthday.
咱俩今天干点什么呢
So, what should we do today?
谢谢你
Oh, I appreciate it,
但你的休息日不用浪费来陪我啦
but you don't have to spend your day off with me.
我不介意啊
Well, I don't mind.
你想去商场里逛逛婴儿用品吗
Oh, you want go to the mall and look at baby stuff?
没兴趣
Not really.
来嘛  我们可以共吃一个椒盐脆饼
Oh, come on, we could share a pretzel
然后被种族歧视老太婆用斜眼瞄
and get sideways glances from racist old ladies.
我带犹太人霍华德
I get enough of that when I take Howard
回我奶奶家过圣诞时就体验过了
to my grandmother's for Christmas.
我知道了
Oh, I know,
我们可以开始收拾出婴儿房啊
why don't we get started on clearing out the baby's room?
这会不会有点太早了啊
Isn't it a little early for that?
早晚都得收拾
You have to get to it eventually.
里面堆了超多垃圾  太不好意思了
Oh, there's so much junk in there, it's embarrassing.
你怎么能在我面前觉得不好意思呢
How can you be embarrassed around me?
到时候我还会陪你进产房呢
I'm gonna be in the room with you when you give birth.
我觉得你不会
I don't think you are.
你也觉得我今早不会出现在你家厨房
You didn't think I was gonna be in your kitchen this morning,
但我还不是来了
yet here I am.
小子
Hey, kid.
啥
Huh, what?
你看起来很累
You look tired.
你何不来一瓶功能饮料呢
Why don't you have an energy drink?
大家都在喝[吸食]
Everyone's doing it.
不了  谢谢  里面含有咖啡因
Oh, no, thank you, those have caffeine in them.
是我不好  我还以为你很潮呢
Oh, sorry, I thought you were cool.
我是很潮啊
I am cool.
你看这饮料
This is Yoo-hoo,
这是兑水版的巧克力牛奶
chocolate milk's delicious watery cousin.
好吧
All right.
但如果哪天你想体验有超能力的感觉
But if you ever want to feel like you have superpowers,
那就试一瓶这个
try one of these.
超级英雄们使用禁药吗
Superheroes take performance-enhancing chemicals?
那还用说
You bet.
你知道为什么浩克这么强壮吗
You know why Hulk is so strong?
类固醇
Steroids.
你知道为什么蝙蝠侠总是昼伏夜出
You know why Batman wanders around at night
大晚上跟人打架吗
getting into fights?
喝酒了
Scotch.
我的确是有一堆活儿要干
I am facing a great deal of work.
名人效应的确能让我更喜欢某些东西
And I do like things better when famous people also like them.
给
Here.
这瓶我请你
It's on the house.
第一瓶免费吗
The first one's free?
闪电侠  你这样生意怎么没垮
Flash, how do you stay in business?
你想知道我的秘诀吗
You want to know my secret?
我买了漫威的股票
I bought stock in Marvel.
你好  伯特
Hi, Bert.
这是我的朋友佩妮
This is my friend, Penny.
-你好  -快请进
- Hi. - Hey, come on in.
我去放点摇滚[石头]乐
I'll gonna go turn on some rock music.
那是地质学的双关语笑话
That's a geology joke.
伯特是一名地质学家
Bert's a geologist.
也是一名说笑达人
And a joker.
我们早到很久吗
How early are we?
其实我们晚到了一个小时
Oh, actually, we're an hour late.
突然好希望谢尔顿在这儿
I suddenly wish Sheldon was here.
我都不知道该从哪里开始收拾
I don't even know where to begin.
《音乐之声》的女主角曾说
Well, in The Sound of Music, Julie Andrews says,
"让我们从头开始
"Let's start at the very beginning.
那是个适合开始的好地方"
A very good place to start."
我本来还打算从尾开始呢
Oh, I was gonna start at the end.
真是要"谢谢你"呀
Thank God you're here.
我觉得首先需要扔掉的东西是
Well, I think the first thing we should get rid of is
你这态度
that tone.
对不起
Sorry.
我应该留着这个  万一生了个女儿呢
I should probably keep this in case we have a girl.
这小房子真可爱
Oh, that's a nice one.
是你小时候的东西吗
Was it yours when you were little?
我爸爸给我做的
My dad built it for me.
真有爱
Wow, it's so cute.
这个是老公  这个是老婆
This was the husband and this was the wife.
他们会一起去冒险
They'd go out on adventures together.
游山玩水  滑雪骑马
Cruises, skiing, horseback riding.
其实就是用胶带把他们粘在我家狗上
That was really me just duct taping them to our dog.
他们有孩子吗
Oh, and did they have kids?
有啊
They did,
可惜他俩不喜欢孩子
but the mommy and daddy didn't like them,
所以他们把孩子送到
so they shipped them off to an orphanage
我用鞋盒做的孤儿院
I made out of a shoebox.
听了完全不会让人担心啊
Yeah, that's not worrisome at all.
不是每一个女生都梦想当妈
Not every girl dreams about being a mom.
可能有时你觉得永远都不会有小孩
Sometimes you think you're never gonna have kids
结果某天醒来就发现自己怀孕了
and one day you wake up and you're pregnant.
哪怕自己的事业正蒸蒸日上
And it doesn't matter that your career's going great right now
而且从没有过跟老公被粘狗身上
and that you and your husband never even got to go anywhere
去游山玩水的机会
taped to a dog!
我居然为了这个翘了动感单车课
I skipped spin class for this.
他怎么能去这么久
Why is it taking him so long
不就从自动贩售机买瓶喝的吗
to get a drink out of a vending machine?
你估计很难理解
Oh, it's complicated.
他对推开那扇小门
He finds pushing that little door
伸手进机器里拿东西的亲密度  感到不舒服
and reaching up into the machine uncomfortably intimate.
男士们  我准备好开工了
Gentlemen, I am ready to work.
引用《火星救援》的台词"我得用科学大展屎威了"
To quote The Martian, "Let's science the feces out of this!"
我说的是《火星救援》这本书和同名电影
That's The Martian the book and The Martian the movie,
不是《火星人马文》
not Marvin the Martian.
要不也引用一下卡通《火星人马文》好了
Although to quote Marvin the Martian,
"我以火星的名义宣布  这星球归我了"
"I claim this planet in the name of Mars."
你还好吧
Are you okay?
好极了  从来没这么好过
Oh, I'm fantastic, never been better.
我喝了人生第一瓶功能饮料  自我感觉棒棒哒
I had my first energy drink and I feel great.
你们想玩摔跤吗
Hey, you guys want to wrestle?
我们可以掰手腕  掰拇指  泥浆摔跤  相扑
We can do arm, thumb, mud, sumo.
算了  我们不够胖  也没穿着尿布
Nah, we're not fat enough, or wearing diapers.
是你要他保持清醒状态的
You wanted him awake.
我们该只跟对方说话  还是去交际啊
So should we talk to each other or mingle?
我不知道其他人上哪儿了
I don't know where everyone is.
是啊  我是说
Yeah, I mean,
我可以想象他吃了一个或两个客人
I could see him eating one or two guests,
但吃光一群也太扯了吧
but not a whole party.
这派对有点失败
Well, I guess this is kind of a bust.
你们想走就走吧
You don't have to stay.
我要开始打扫了
I'm gonna start cleaning up.
好吧
Okay.
把他扔在这里我会很内疚的
I feel so bad about leaving him here.
真有意思  我刚想扔下你时也觉得内疚
Oh, it's funny, I was just thinking the same thing about you.
听着
Hey, listen,
你能不能别把这件事
could you not say anything about this
告诉大学里的人
to the people at the university?
因为...
You know, 'cause...
你是如此...  而我...  这有点丢人
you're you and I'm me, and it's kind of embarrassing.
等等  "她是如此..."是什么意思
Wait, what do you mean "she's her"?
艾米是大学里最酷的女生  不是吗
Well, you know how Amy's the coolest girl on campus, right?
-当然不是  -当然不是
- No. - No.
真的  大家都这么觉得
Oh yeah, everybody thinks so.
什么
What?
你得了脚气就告诉我  反而这事藏着掖着啊
You tell me about your foot fungus, but this is a secret?
我敢说肯定是因为我的男友是谢尔顿
I'm sure it's just 'cause I'm dating Sheldon.
老实说  谢尔顿之所以受欢迎
Mm, actually, I think Sheldon's popular
是因为他的女友是你
because he's dating you.
现在谢尔顿居然受人欢迎了
Now Sheldon's popular?
到底是什么状况啊
What is happening?
或许我们该休息吃个午餐
Maybe we should break for lunch.
几点了
What time is it?
史上最烂的布谷鸟报时钟刚说  两点了
According to the world's worst cuckoo clock, it's 2:00.
我的头好疼
My head hurts
我此生第一次这么累
and I'm more tired than ever.
你干嘛不回家
Why don't you just go home?
不  我能撑下去
No, I can do this.
我...我只需再来一瓶功能饮料
I just, I just need another energy drink.
糟糕
Oh, no.
怎么了
What?
我想再来一瓶
I want another one.
所以呢
So?
那是一种渴求
That's a craving.
药物依赖的征兆
That's a sign of chemical dependency.
你才喝了一瓶
You only had one.
不  我知道
No, I know,
但很多事物只要试一次就会上瘾
but plenty of things are addictive after a single exposure.
比如说可卡因  尼古丁  品客薯片
I mean, crack cocaine, nicotine, Pringles.
根本停不下来
You know once one pops one just can't stop.
你哪有可能这么快就染上瘾
You can't develop a problem that fast.
你要打赌吗  这下好了
You want to bet? Oh, great,
我现在还染上赌瘾了
now I'm addicted to gambling.
我们没时间浪费了
We can't afford to lose any more time.
虽然可能没多大用  但你们曾经试过
Well, this probably won't work, but has anyone ever tried
运起12成功力  打他个茅塞顿开吗
to just haul off and whoop the crazy out of him?
这个建议完全没有帮助
That's not helpful.
虽然想起来爽翻了  但没有实质帮助
It's fun to think about, but it's not helpful.
谢尔顿  我们时间非常紧张
Hey, Sheldon, we are on a serious time crunch.
没有你我们根本完成不了
We can't do this without you.
拜托你别演大戏了好不好
Can you please pull it together?
抱歉  我会好好振作的
I'm sorry. Yes, of course.
谢了
Thank you.
也请两位在我出现
Just, please, bear with me
咖啡因脱瘾症状时尽量包容一下
if I display symptoms of caffeine withdrawal.
没问题
No worries.
你们俩身上好臭
You guys stink.
抱歉对你发脾气了
Sorry I flipped out on you.
都是这孕期荷尔蒙惹的祸
I think it's just hormones.
我看你怀孕前就是一副晚娘脸了
I think you were mean before you were pregnant,
不过没关系
but it's fine.
咱们先暂缓收拾房间吧
So, uh, instead of cleaning out the room,
不如先决定一下婴儿房的主题怎么样
why don't we just decide on a theme for the nursery?
婴儿房还需要主题吗
Does it really need one?
当然需要了
Of course it does.
你小时候的闺房没有主题吗
Didn't your baby room have a theme?
我的闺房同时也是我爸的办公室
Well, it doubled as my dad's office,
他又是个警察
and he was a cop,
所以主题大概就是鲜血淋漓的凶案照片
so I guess the theme was bloody homicide photos.
我的主题是小熊维尼
Oh. Mine was Winnie the Pooh.
总之...
But anyway...
我们先从最基本的开始
why don't we just take a step back
先挑一个颜色吧
and start with a color?
颜色的挑选可就五花八门了
Right? There are so many amazing ones.
红色啊  蓝色啊  绿色啊  紫色啊...
Red, blue, green, purple...
你是不是要把所有的颜色都说一遍啊
Are you just gonna name all the colors?
你这样我不敢说了
Well, not now.
房间什么颜色随便啦
I don't care what color the room is.
好  好  我只是想帮你而已
Okay, well, I'm just trying to help you.
帮忙个屁  闭嘴吧
Well, you're not, so just drop it!
人家明显不开心了  你为啥还不跟过来
I'm clearly upset. Why aren't you following me?
这就来  这就来
Sorry! Sorry!
当艾米开始用铬酸和白醋的调和剂
And when Amy started using a solution of chromic acid
清洗她的实验室器材后
and white vinegar to clean all her lab equipment,
瞬时间  每个人都开始这么做了
all of a sudden, everybody was doing it.
你真是潮流引导者啊
You trend setter!
我只是在恰当的时间做了恰当的事
Just the right idea at the right time.
好了好了  艾米很酷  谢尔顿也很酷
Okay, okay, so Amy's cool, Sheldon's cool.
-再跟我说说莱纳德  -谁啊
- Tell me about Leonard. - Who?
莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德
Leonard Hofstadter.
他啊  他还凑合吧
Oh, him. I guess he's all right.
他貌似骗到了一个大美女结婚呢
Apparently he tricked some hot girl into marrying him.
大美女就是我
That's me, I'm her.
他没有骗我啦
You know, he didn't trick me.
他只是纠缠得放弃挣扎而已
He just wore me down.
怪不得你俩是好闺蜜
It makes sense you two are friends.
美女们总是抱团玩在一起
I mean, hot girls always stick together.
你之前还觉得这个派对不会好玩呢
And you thought this wasn't gonna be a great party.
我还真没想到
You know, I had no idea
加州理工大学和我高中简直是一样一样的
Caltech is exactly like my high school.
也不是完全一样啦
Well, it's not exactly like it.
我们都是智商超群的人
We're all extremely smart.
你这种受欢迎的妹子嘴还真毒
Wow... you popular girls are mean.
我要去煮点咖啡了  你要喝吗
I'm gonna get some coffee. You want some?
人家正在努力将生活拉回正轨中
Uh, you're really going to have caffeine in front of me
你却要在我面前摄入咖啡因吗
when I'm trying to get my life back on track?
好了  我们假设你的确有咖啡因上瘾的问题
Uh, okay, let's pretend you do have a problem.
-的确有  -才没有
- I do. - You don't.
-我真有问题  -你才没有问题
- Yeah, but I do. - No, you don't!
让我们假设你有问题
But let's say you do.
不要说你有  因为你没有
And don't say you do, because you don't!
如果真是这样  那么全身心地投入工作
Now, wouldn't you think that throwing yourself
难道不是解决上瘾问题的最好方式吗
into your work would be the best way to deal with it?
-解决什么  -你的问题
- With what? - Your problem.
你不是说我没有问题吗
I thought I didn't have a problem.
真是惨得不忍直视啊
That was painful to watch.
我们这是要去哪儿啊
So where are we going?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
好一对末路狂花
How Thelma and Louise of us.
拉杰  你说我为什么不上心呢
Raj, why don't I care about anything?
你说什么
I'm sorry?
这明明是我的孩子
It's my baby.
我应该会在意婴儿房  颜色之类的事
I-I should care about nurseries and colors,
但我却毫不关心  我到底有什么毛病
and I don't-- what's wrong with me?
很可能和你摇篮边的罪案现场照片有关
Well, crime-scene photos near your crib spring to mind.
我一直在等着自己能兴奋起来
I keep waiting to feel excited,
可那种感觉迟迟没有降临
but it's not happening.
如果我一直感觉不到兴奋怎么办
What if it never happens?
博纳黛特  别这样
Bernadette, come on, look,
你想太多了
you're overthinking this, okay?
你会成为一位很棒的妈妈的
You're gonna be an amazing mom.
就算你自己不相信
Even if you don't believe it,
我知道你具有母性本能
I know you have maternal instincts.
有一次  我负责照顾我弟弟们
Once, I was supposed to babysit my brothers.
结果邻居发现他们光着屁股在后院捉蟋蟀吃
Our neighbor found them naked in the backyard eating crickets.
玩得开心  吃得满意
Happy and well-fed.
你看  我从你的故事里听出了这两优点
You see, that's what I'm taking from that story.
莱纳德  我能问你个问题吗
Leonard, can I ask you a question?
是有关你应该解决的轴对称问题
Is it about the rotational symmetries you should be figuring out
还是你假装的咖啡因上瘾问题
or your fake caffeine problem?
霍华德  我能问你个问题吗
Howard, can I ask you a question?
不行
No.
就当我对着空气说话吧
All right, I'll just toss this out to the room.
我在想对抗瘾头的最好办法
Um, I was thinking that the best way
应该是一步一步脱瘾
to fight my addiction is by weaning myself off in steps.
我找不到戒咖啡因贴片
Now, I couldn't find a caffeine patch,
但我找到了一个号称
but I did find what claims to be
能震荡五脏六腑的咖啡因栓剂
a mind-boosting caffeine suppository.
没错
Yeah.
讲一个关于直肠的有趣知识...
You know, the interesting fact about the rectum...
谢尔顿
Sheldon!
我们有着难以达成的截止日期
We are dealing with an impossible deadline
而且还是拜你所赐
from the Air Force because of you.
所以喝功能饮料  不喝功能饮料
So have an energy drink, don't have an energy drink.
买肛门栓剂  你爱塞哪就塞哪
Order suppositories and shove 'em wherever you want,
我才懒得管你
I don't care!
不用塞
You don't shove them.
它自带润滑导入器
They come with an easy-glide applicator.
好的  听我说
Right. Listen to me.
你不做好你那部分  我们什么都做不了
We can't do anything until you do your part.
所以赶快到白板跟前  做你该做的事
So get up in front of this whiteboard and do it!
-我做不到  -当然能做
- I can't. - Yes, you can.
不是
No...
我算不出来
I can't figure out the math.
这几天我绞尽脑汁
I've been racking my brain for days,
还是一无所获
and I've got nothing.
真的吗
Seriously?
我做不到
I can't do it.
我并没有我以为的那么聪明
I'm not as smart as I think I am.
对不起  都是我的错
I'm so sorry. This is all my fault.
没关系  我们会想到办法的
It's okay, we'll figure something out.
万一想不到呢
But what if we can't?
会好的
It'll be fine.
慢慢来
You'll see.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
兄弟
Buddy?
等宝宝出世了
When the baby gets here,
你必须教会我这招
you gotta teach me that.
非常感谢  伯特  今天很愉快
Thank you so much, Bert. This was great.
我的荣幸
My pleasure.
两位姑娘要不要
You girls want to take home
带7.5升的土豆沙拉回家
a two-gallon tub of potato salad?
不用了吧
I think we're good.
好的  谢谢你们能来
Okay, well, thanks for coming by.
你们真是好人
You're nice people.
你也是  你知道吗
Well, so are you. In fact, you know what?
你的好  大恩不"岩"谢
We will never take you for granite.
听出双关语没  花岗"岩"
Did you get that? Granite?
小小地质学笑话
A little geology joke.
你们快走吧
You need to leave.
我有点爱上你们俩了
I'm in love with both of you now.
-是  -再见
- Okay. - Bye.
靠边停
Uh, pull over.
什么  怎么了  你给谁打电话呢
What? Why? Who are you calling?
你要跟霍华德打小报告是不是
You're gonna rat me out to Howard, aren't you?
居然还会告密  难怪我一直看你不顺眼
You're such a snitch, no wonder I don't like you.
我是打给我爸好吗
Whoa, I'm calling my dad, okay?
他对孕妇们的事很有经验
He's got experience dealing with pregnant ladies
因为他是妇科医师
because he's an OBGYN.
对付疯婆子也很有经验
And experience with crazy ladies
因为有我妈
because of my mom.
拉杰什
Hello, Rajesh.
你打电话是来要钱的吗
Are you calling to ask for money?
什么  不是
What? No.
你打电话是来要需要花钱的东西吗
Are you calling to ask for things that cost money?
不是
No.
那很好  有何关照
Great. What's up?
这是我朋友  伯纳黛特
This is my friend, Bernadette.
她怀孕了  心里有些烦恼
She's pregnant, and she's a bit worried,
我想或许你能跟她聊聊
so I thought maybe you could talk to her.
当然可以  有什么烦恼
Of course. What seems to be the trouble?
心里觉得有些怪怪的
Something's wrong.
我对孩子的东西毫无兴趣
I don't care about any of the baby stuff
不像其他妈妈那么痴迷
every other mom is so into.
说实话  我都不确定自己是否喜欢孩子
Honestly, I'm not even sure I like babies.
听着  有些人喜欢小孩
Look, some people are baby people,
有些人不喜欢小孩
and some people are not baby people.
但这不代表你不爱自己的孩子啊
It doesn't mean you won't love your own baby.
我以为自己会更兴奋呢
But I thought I'd be more excited.
兴奋也不能保证什么啊
Oh, being excited isn't a guarantee of anything.
拉杰什的妈妈怀他的时候  兴奋得不行
Rajesh's mother was thrilled when she was pregnant with him.
他出生以后  一举一动都让她痴迷不已
After he was born, she doted on his every move.
知道后来怎么了吗
And you know what happened?
他伤了妈妈的心  搬到地球另一端去
He broke her heart, moved halfway around the world,
只跟穷酸的可怜白人姑娘约会
and dates only poor white women.
世事难料啊
So you never know.
谢谢您  我感觉好多了
Thank you. I feel better now.
-我感觉不好  -很好
- I don't! - Good.
伯纳黛特  祝你生个千金
Bernadette, I hope you have a daughter.
我不知道该怎么开口
Uh...I don't know how to say this.
可以试试用"长官"开头
Well, you could try starting with "sir".
对  对不起  长官
Right. Sorry, sir.
他说的是开头  不是结尾
He said start with it, not end with it.
长官
Sir...
我们碰到了一些难关
We've hit a bit of a snag.
赶不上计划时间了
We're already behind schedule.
计算需要克服的部署性问题
The computations required to
要比我们之前预想的
overcome the deployability issues
要大了许多
are more significant than we thought.
我知道我们签了合同
I understand that we're under contract,
不知道违反合同有什么后果
and I don't know what the consequences of violating that are,
但是  我们没办法
but, uh... we're not gonna be able to deliver
按保证的时间完成了
in the time we promised.
你们需要多久
How long do you need?
我们估计...  两年吧
We-We're thinking... two years.
好的
All right.
就这样
That's it?
你愿意接受啊
You're okay with that?
你觉得你是第一个
You think you're the first government contractor
无法按时完成政府合同的人吗
who isn't gonna deliver on time?
我们还在等当年里根总统
We're still waiting for a big space laser
订来打共产党的大宇宙镭射枪呢
Reagan ordered to beat the commies.
感谢您的理解  长官
Thanks for understanding, sir.
非常感谢
Yes, thank you so much.
我们真的很感激
We-We really appreciate it.
好了  没压力了
All right, pressure's off
要去看电影吗
Wanna see a movie?
爆米花我请
Popcorn's on me.